the72.co.uk 2018-06-01

# Privacy Policy - The72

### Advertising

This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

#### DoubleClick for Publishers (Google Inc.)

DoubleClick for Publishers is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. that allows the Owner to run advertising campaigns in conjunction with external advertising networks that the Owner, unless otherwise specified in this document, has no direct relationship with. In order to opt out from being tracked by various advertising networks, Users may make use of [Youronlinechoices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). In order to understand Google’s use of data, consult [Google’s partner policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).  
This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

#### Criteo (Criteo SA)

Criteo is an advertising service provided by Criteo SA.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: France – [Privacy Policy](http://www.criteo.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://www.criteo.com/deactivate-criteo-banners/).

#### AppNexus (AppNexus Inc.)

AppNexus is an advertising service provided by AppNexus Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices).

#### Rubicon Project (The Rubicon Project, Inc.)

Rubicon Project is an advertising service provided by The Rubicon Project, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/).

#### Index Exchange (Index Exchange)

Index Exchange is an advertising service provided by Index Exchange.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

#### GumGum (GumGum, Inc.)

GumGum is an advertising service provided by GumGum, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://gumgum.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out](https://gumgum.com/opt-out).

#### 152 Media (152 Media, LLC.)

152 Media is an advertising service provided by 152 Media, LLC.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.152media.com/privacy.html) – [Opt Out](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/8a17cf9b-19c4-4f99-a32d-4dd3b0f21c93).

#### Google AdSense (Google Inc.)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this Website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.  
Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

#### Taboola Monetize Content (Taboola Inc.)

Taboola is an advertising service provided by Taboola Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy) – [Opt Out](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy). 

#### Sublime Skinz (Sublime Skinz Labs)

Sublime Skinz is an advertising service provided by Sublime Skinz Labs

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. 

Place of processing: France – [Privacy Policy](http://sublimeskinz.com/privacy-en) – [Opt Out](mailto:privacy@sublimeskinz.com). 

## Privacy Policy:

The72 (" **The72** ") operates the72.co.uk and may operate other websites. It is The72's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, The72 collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The72's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how The72's visitors use its website. From time to time, The72 may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

The72 also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on the72.co.uk blogs/sites. The72 only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to The72's websites choose to interact with The72 in ways that require The72 to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that The72 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [the72.co.uk](http://the72.co.uk/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with The72 are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, The72 collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with The72. The72 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

The72 may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. The72 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, The72 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

The72 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on The72's behalf or to provide services available at The72's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using The72's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. The72 will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, The72 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when The72 believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of The72, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an The72 website and have supplied your email address, The72 may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with The72 and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. The72 takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The72 uses cookies to help The72 identify and track visitors, their usage of The72 website, and their website access preferences. The72 visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using The72's websites, with the drawback that certain features of The72's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If The72, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that The72 goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of The72 may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by The72 and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, The72 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in The72's sole discretion. The72 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a the72.co.uk account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
